

WALTER RADDUSO FrontEnd Developer

ABOUT ME

I was born in San Justo, Santa Fe, Argentina on February 10, 1986. A couple of years ago I've moved to Santa Fe City in Argentina.

When I was younger I loved computers, many years ago I met the language C and created my first application. Then I met PHP and that's when I discovered my real passion, being a web developer. Since then, I kept myself continuously learning and improving the way of writing better code, everyday.

- **CONTACT ME**
- Santa Fe, Argentina
- w.radduso@gmail.com
- +54 9 3498 402 997
- **MY SKILLS**
- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- React
- React Native
- NodeJS
- PHP
- MySQL
- MongoDB



WORK EXPERIENCE

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Endeev SRL



Inside of the company I have a very dynamic role, executing lots of tasks in different environments. I'm the team leader of a web application created with CakePHP in the Backend and HTML, CSS, JQuery, AngularJS and most recently, VueJs in the FrontEnd. Also, I helped the product manager with tasks like designing new features or validating requirements. I've worked for several months as a FrontEnd developer creating applications using AngularJS and React. I've developed some mobile application using React Native. Nowadays I've been working with NodeJs, creating an API Rest.

WEB DEVELOPER

Freelancer

Feb 2016 - Jun 2016

I was continued my freelance working. In this case I was in charge of create the site of the city (municipality of San Justo, Santa Fe) with a module of news (like a online newspaper) and a internal system to manage the users complain.

WEB/MOBILE DEVELOPER

I've been working in an application for swimmers only for iOS (Objective-C). Also in charge of a website in WordPress, we created a plugin which got products from a web application (RESTful API). The plugin created products in woocomerce to sell in the website.

WEB DEVELOPER

Tecnosan

iii Oct 2013 - Sep 2014

I've worked on several projects with different business rules and all kind of web applications. My job was to create and maintenance web applications (PHP, HTML, CSS, JS and MySQL).

WEB DEVELOPER

Freelancer

May 2011 - Oct 2013

I've been working on several kind of projects (PHP, HTML, CSS and JS), custom and complex WordPress sites, RESTful APIs, and also building entire applications including User Interfaces. One of my own projects was a local e-commerce where users were able to upload products and sell them. The site was used in San Justo, Santa Fe and surrounding area.



EDUCATION

IT SUPERIOR TECHNICIAN

instituto Superior N°20

1 2012 - 2014

SUPERIOR TECHNICIAN IN APPLIED IT

universidad Tecnológica Nacional - Uncomplete

2008 - 2011

SECONDARY SCHOOL

Escuela de Comercio Dr. Roberto Gonzalez Nº 45

2008 - 2003



LANGUAGES

SPANISH

ENGLISH

